martinmadsen software developer, me@martinbjeldbak.com

about

7/56 Hood St Sherwood 4075 Queensland Australia

28 years old +61 413 043 210 martinbjeldbak.com / martinbjeldbak in / martinbjeldbak

languages

bilingual Danish/English IELTS score: 8.5

programming

Ruby on Rails Heroku, AWS (EC2, RDS, ECS, S3), SQL CircleCI, GitHub Actions LATEX, HTML, Git JavaScript (ES6, React) OS X, Unix

interests

machine learning, devOps TDD, functional programming service oriented architecture web development

experience

since 2020

Software Engineer working on the ANZx team within ANZ. 2016 - 2020 **Lead Software Developer, Backend** NetEngine, Brisbane, Australia Ruby on Rails software developer working with our clients to build web-based systems across many different industries, from finance to flood mapping. I work on setting up infrastructure in AWS using CloudFormation, to building service objects in Rails and avoiding circular dependencies. I also partake in non-technical activities such as business planning, training new backend developers, etc. **Student Software Developer** 2012-2014 Falck Healthcare a/s, Aalborg, Denmark

Development of Ruby on Rails-based system used daily by ca. 40 of Falck's physiotherapists to journal their patients' treatments and wellbeing.

ANZ Bank, Melbourne, Australia

University of California, San Diego, O

Founder Divambu (shut down) Ran my own small company developing and hosting web sites for clients.

education

2010-2014

2014-2016

M.Sc. in Computer Science Aalborg University (AAU), Denmark Majoring in Computer Science (120 ECTS) Specializing in Machine Intelligence Studying abroad University of California, San Diego (UCSD), USA 2014-2015 Fully accredited as part of the first year of my master's degree from Aalborg University **B.Sc.** in Computer Science 2011-2014 Aalborg University (AAU), Denmark Majoring in Computer Science (180 ECTS) 2008-2011 EUC Nord - Technical Gymnasium of Hjørring, Denmark Focus in physics and engineering

other activities

XQuery Processor

2013-2014 Student member of the Study Board Aalborg University (AAU), Denmark Elected position. Handling of educations within Computer Science curricula at the university, quality assurance of education, handling of exemptions, etc.

projects

2015

| | martinbjeldbak/xquery-processor |
|------|--|
| | Implemented a subset of the XQuery and XPath XML query languages in Java |
| 2016 | A Hierarchical Tree Distance Measure for Classification martin bjeldbak.com/thesis.pdf |
| | Concluded my M.Sc. degree. Published in Proceedings of the 6th International Con- |
| | ference on Pattern Recognition Applications and Methods - Volume 1: ICPRAM 2017, |
| | pages 502-509 |